getwizer.com 2019-03-22

# Privacy policy - Wizer

  1. Wizer Feedback Ltd. (the “ **Company** “) is committed to your right to privacy. Your use of the Company’s website and/or application (the “ **Site** “) and the Services are governed by the Agreement and this privacy policy (the “ **Privacy Policy** “). This Privacy Policy shall be considered as an integral part of the Agreement. Capitalized terms used but not defined herein shall have the meanings ascribed to them in the Agreement available at <https://www.getwizer.comterms-of-service/>.

  2. If you choose to use, register or submit information to the Site, System and/or Services, you agree to the use of such data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You may not use the Site, System or the Services or submit any information to the Company if you do not agree to any of the terms hereunder. Please note, that the Services may contain links to other sites maintained by third parties, which are not governed by this Privacy Policy. The Company is not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. You should review the applicable privacy policies of any third parties before providing them with any personally identifiable information.

### Collection of Data

  3. We log visitor’s domain, IP address, region and other device identifiers automatically; this information identifies only the computer or device that is being used to view the Site or access the Services. We also use cookies (small text files stored in a user’s browser) or Web beacons (electronic images that allow the website to count visitors who have accessed a particular page and to access certain cookies) to gather personally unidentified information. You may at any time program your browser or change your device’s settings to block cookies and other identifiers, but be aware that such blocking may prevent us from providing some or all of the Services to you. We may also log information regarding positions you entered in your account, duration of stay on the website, and other information regarding use of the Site and Services.

  4. Other than with respect to Personal Data (as defined below), if you provide information via the Services, you agree that we have unlimited rights to such information and that we may use such information in any way we choose. Such information shall be deemed to be non-confidential.

### Collection of Personal Data

  5. We collect only Personal Data that is specifically and voluntarily provided by you, for example, when you register for an account, we collect your username, password and email address.

  6. The term “ **Personal Data** ” when used in this Privacy Policy refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, cell phone number, mailing and email address, passwords, billing details and any other personal information submitted by you through the Site or Services.

  7. We constructed the Services with the clear understanding that your Personal Data is private and that it should not be accessible to anyone, unless as otherwise specified hereunder, and subject to Section ‎16 below.

### Use of Data and Marketing Communications

  8. Non-personal information is used mainly for click stream analysis in order to constantly improve and maintain our Services, including among others, for ensuring the technical functioning of the System, to help prevent fraudulent use of our Services and for developing new services and features.

  9. We may also share non-personal, aggregate information regarding Service usage with our affiliates, partners and advertisers. From time to time, we may release non-Personal Data in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in our Services usage.

  10. We also use the non-personal information provided by you via the Services in connection with the generation of the Customer’s Questionnaire, by disclosing such non-personal information to Respondents and/or third party business partners. You hereby acknowledge and consent to the use and transfer of such non-personal information as required for the generation of the Customer’s Questionnaire.

  11. Personal Data is used only for limited purposes such as to store user preferences, to contact you in response to requests or inquiries, to carry out the Services, or to optimize the content we display and personalize your experience.

  12. We may send users of the Site or Services who provided us with their contact details, information on special offers, products, features, activities, services and periodic announcements or newsletters. By accepting this Privacy Policy you hereby provide us with your explicit, written consent to receive marketing communications. You may at any time choose to opt-out and to not receive these communications, by contacting us at <https://www.getwizer.comcontact-us/>

  13. We may also use Personal Data to communicate with you regarding customer service issues. These communications are not promotional in nature. When you send communications to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and/or improve our Services.

### Payment Information

  14. If you provide credit card, debit card or other applicable payment information to complete a purchase, you hereby agree and acknowledge that it is our policy to use third-party payment processing systems that comply with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS), which is an industry wide security standard designed to protect the confidentiality and security of your credit card information, by encryption using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and storage with AES-256 encryption. Your payment information may also be subject to our payment processor’s privacy policy in addition to ours. PLEASE READ THE PRIVACY POLICY ON THE WEBSITE OF ANY PAYMENT PROCESSOR THAT YOU ARE DIRECTED TO REGARDING THE USE, STORAGE AND PROTECTION OF YOUR CREDIT CARD INFORMATION BEFORE SUBMITTING ANY PAYMENT INFORMATION.

### Disclosure of Data

    15. We do not share or distribute your Personal Data with unrelated third parties, except under limited circumstances, such as to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or the Site, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event.

### Protection of Data

    16. We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your Personal Data as are customary in the industry with similar sites. Nevertheless, these security measures cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with personal information. Therefore, the Company shall not be liable for any damages caused by unauthorized access to your Personal Data and/or to your Account.

### Transfer of Data Abroad

    17. The Company is a global enterprise and may maintain facilities and databases in different countries. We may, from time to time, transfer your Personal Data to one of our databases in another country. If the level of privacy protection in a country does not comply with recognized international standards, we will ensure that data transferred to our databases in that country is adequately protected and that the transfer of data to third parties in such countries is made pursuant to a contract or other measures providing adequate protection.

    18. Of course, the Internet is made up of a large number of international connections. If you are visiting the Site or Services from a country other than the country in which our server is located, the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. We may also use hosting services located in other countries at our sole discretion, which will necessitate transfers of data. By using the Site or the Services and communicating electronically with us, you explicitly and unequivocally consent to transfers of data as specified hereunder.

### Third-Party Applications

    19. The Company may share your non-personal information with a third party application with your consent, for example when you choose to access our Site and/or Services through such an application. We are not responsible for what those third parties do with your information, so you should make sure you trust the application and that it has a privacy policy acceptable to you.

### Amending or Deleting Your Information

    20. If you are a registered user, you may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Data you have provided us in your registration or account profile by accessing your “account settings”, and amending the relevant information. If you wish to delete your Personal Data please contact us at <https://www.getwizer.comcontact-us/>. If your Personal Data changes, or if you cancel your use of our Services, you may update it by making the change on your account settings.

### Use of the Services

    21. The Services are not intended for use if you are under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 16 or knowingly allow such persons to register as users. By using the Site and/or Services you represent that you are at least 16 years old.

### Miscellaneous

    22. This Privacy Policy together with the Agreement comprises the entire agreement between you and the Company relating to the Site and the Services. We may change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review this page regularly.

    23. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or wish to give us any notice, you may do so by email to <https://www.getwizer.comcontact-us/>
